hostpair.com 2017-05-04

# Privacy Policy

This is ExonHost LLC Privacy Policy. It discusses how we will collect, use, maintain and disclose the information which we will collect from our website visitors and customers. Our privacy policy is part of our contracts. It is incorporated into our TOS and any other contract we have with users. 

**What type of information does collect by ExonHost LLC?**

When a visitor visit our website our web server collects basic user information about you that includes your ISP's domain, the time you accessed our Web site, and the pages from within our Web site that you visit and is not personally identifiable information except as needed to prevent fraud or abuse of the system. 

When a customer order our service we collocted following information:

  * Traditional contact information such as mailing address, phone number, and fax number.
  * Internet contact information such as email addresses.
  * Credit card information.
  * Information about the user's computer system, such as the web browser type, IP address, and operating system.
  * Non-financial identification information, such as username and password combinations.

**Why is this website collecting traditional contact information?**

We collect traditional contact information for the following purposes:

  * For billing and support purposes.
  * For domain registration account establishment.
  * For website administration purposes.
  * To customise the website for the user on multiple visits to the site.

**How We Use Information**

We do not share, rent, sell or release your personal information to any individual, entity or third party.

ExonHost LLC may use personally identifiable information collected through our Web site to contact Users regarding products and services offered by ExonHost LLC and its trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners, and otherwise to enhance customers experience with ExonHost LLC and such affiliates, independent contractors and business partners. ExonHost LLC may also use information collected through our Web site for research regarding the effectiveness of the Web site and the marketing, advertising and sales efforts of ExonHost LLC, its trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners; for example, to provide you with information about products which might be of interest to you or to enable you to take advantage of special partner programs or ExonHost LLC specials. ExonHost LLC may also use customer information to provide customers with system information or information about new or upgraded products.

We may disclose contact information with your permission when gathering and posting testimonials.

We will not otherwise disclose customer personal and account information unless we have reason to believe that disclosing such information is necessary to identify, make contact with, or bring legal action against someone who may be causing harm or interfering with the rights or property of ExonHost LLC, our customers, or others. We may provide information to regulatory authorities and law enforcement officials in accordance with applicable laws or where ExonHost LLC has a good faith belief that the law requires such disclosure.

**What if I think that you are not adhering to this statement?**

If you believe we are not handling your information in accordance with our privacy policy, please contact us.If for some reason we have violated our privacy policy, we will correct the error as soon as you notify us.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

From time to time, we may change our Privacy Policy. We will post those changes on this page so that our customers will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we share the information with others.

#### Subscribe to our Newsletter
